# **SUMAN LAMA**

## Web Designer, Graphic Designer and Artist

www.sumanjlama.com sumanjlama@gmail.com

I am currently searching for an opportunity to work within a creative design-oriented team. I am highly IT proficient and can code in HTML, CSS, and fundamental JavaScript. In addition, I have strong experience in producing contents with Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator and XD.

Skilled in graphic design, web design and basic front-end development I am an inquisitive and a motivated person, who is keen to learn and explore solutions to always achieve the best result.

I also have a keen interest on music, photography, and sports.

### **Work Experience**

# Digital and Graphics Designer JHR Nature Cure

July 2019 – Present

I am the sole designer for this supplement production team. My accomplishments for the team include:

- Designing:
  - o Company Logo
  - o Products' branding and Logos
  - Marketing Campaigns
  - o E-commerce website
- Taking photos and updating their websites with new contents (Applicable at present).
- Contributing to laying out strategies for public related communications directly to the manager.

#### Sales

#### Firewood and Solid Fuel Center

September 2016 – Present

I work with a small team supervised by a manager to run this heating supply business. My contributions to the team include:

- Attending to our customers enquiries and successfully ensuring that they benefit from our services to satisfaction.
- Dealing with administrative tasks such as replying emails and making phone calls.
- Coordinating and allotting delivery schedules by consulting with the clients.
- Supervising and training part-time and new staffs on weekends.

#### Education

### Bachelor's in Fine Art Printmaking

*University of Brighton - Brighton and Hove* 2013 to 2016

## Foundation degree in Art and Design

Stroud College - Stroud 2012 to 2013

## A Levels in English Language, Media studies and Fine Art

*Cirencester College - Cirencester* 2010 to 2012

#### **Skills**

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator Adobe XD

Microsoft Office

Html CSS

Bootstrap JavaScript